{
    "subject": "resource/Auntie_Mame_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Forrest_Tucker",
    "human_readable": "Auntie Mame (film) stars Forrest Tucker.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8697167038917542,
            "question": "Who stars in the film Auntie Mame?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7356823682785034,
            "question": "In what movie does Forrest Tucker play a lead role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.734424352645874,
            "question": "Is Forrest Tucker an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7276089191436768,
            "question": "What is the name of the film featuring Forrest Tucker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7217369079589844,
            "question": "Who directed Auntie Mame?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7120971083641052,
            "question": "Was Auntie Mame a successful film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6637091636657715,
            "question": "What genre is the film Auntie Mame?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43632444739341736,
            "question": "Are there any sequels or remakes of Auntie Mame?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41955769062042236,
            "question": "When was Auntie Mame released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3768649399280548,
            "question": "What are some themes explored in Auntie Mame?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Auntie Mame (film) stars Forrest Tucker.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3104_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Auntie Mame released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3104_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any sequels or remakes of Auntie Mame?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3104_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Auntie Mame?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3104_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3104_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3104_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3104_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3104_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3104_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3104_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3104_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3104_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3104_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3104_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the information in the documents supports the triple. The film \"Auntie Mame\" has a cast listed, which includes Rosalind Russell and Forrest Tucker, among others."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe document states that the film \"Auntie Mame\" features actors including \"Rosalind Russell, Forrest Tucker, Coral Browne, Fred Clark, Roger Smith, Patric Knowles, Peggy Cass, Jan Handzlik, Joanna Barnes, Pippa Scott, Lee Patrick\", which confirms that Forrest Tucker starred in the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}